ROBERT TRAN

DOB Address

12/09/1997 10 Solomon Crescent, Tingalpa

Phone Email Portfolio

0451129979 rtran.nvtt@gmail.com https://roberttran.vercel.app/



ABOUT ME

I am a one year junior web developer with a passion in making front-end UI/UX design using different libraries such as React.js, Tailwindcss, Bootstrap, MUI, Three.js. Currently I'm learning about back-end development including Node.js, Express.js, Firebase and also doing freelance work. I want to continue learning and growing my technical skill not only in front-end, but also back-end development with node.js, database management and web hosting.

EDUCATION HISTORY

2016-2019

Bachelor of Information Technology

Queensland University Of

Technology

- Basic and advanced methods of web development
- Mostly played developer role in teamwork.

2020 - 2021

Professional Year at Navitas

- 3-month Internship at Centra Networks.
- Developed Professional Communication skills
- Developed the "Work hard Play hard" approach to life and work.

WORK EXPERIENCE

3/2023 - 4/2023

Freelance Web developer, Le Bakery & Patisserie

- -Design and Create https://lebakery.com.au/ website using Wordpress, custom CSS and Javascript.
- -Set up Domain and hosting.
- -Set up online menu order for customer, with payment through stripe.
- -Implementing SEO and Google Search Console

6/2022 - 11/2022

Junior Web Developer, Pakko

- -Maintain and update main website at https://Pakko.com.au/ with Wordpress.
- -Design and create different web templates for internal usage.
- -Create layout for IDP project at https://idp.pakko.com.au/
- -Implement different UI/UX design/functionality for the IDP project, including: changing box color, control box with a 3d view cube, design options for customer when clicking on different surfaces
- -Custom image editor for IDP with fabric.js. Apply the image saved in the image editor to the panel.
- -Back-end development with node.js

11/2020-2/2021

Web Developer/Designer Internship, Centra Networks

- -Learn how to make and modify designs with photoshop.
- -Design and implement service ticket template.
- -Modify posters for CSAT (Centra Security Awareness Training) for internal use.
- -Create a new catalogue design to introduce Centra Networks, with update of terms, services and conditions.
- -Implement a referral page for the referral campaign.

PROJECTS

Personal Website: https://roberttran.vercel.app/

-Personal Portfolio Website using next.js, tailwindcss, GraphCMS and deployed on Vercel

Post and Comment Website: https://writero.netlify.app/

-Simple Post and Comment Website with next.js, tailwindcss, firebase

Wordpress website: https://khoastories.com/

-Portfolio Website using Wordpress

Wix style website: https://www.tranfoodphotography.com/

-Food Portfolio and Blog site using Wix

University Music Website Project (Graduation Project)

-Make Music school website with pure HTML,CSS, Javascript and deployed locally with XAMPP

SKILLS

Front-end: HTML/CSS, Javascript, React.js/Next.js, Wordpress, Bootstrap, MaterialUI, Tailwindcss, Typescript, React Three Fiber

Back-end: Node.js, Express.js, Firebase, Pdfkit, Mongodb (Progressing)

Others: Heroku, Github, Netlify, Vercel, AWS Amplify